{
    "id": "f35ad677400740aea3aff1eca55640d2",
    "title": "Comparison Of Adjectives",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This is …………………………. than that.",
            "description": "Use a comparative adjective before than.",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "better",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "478c9a63803e45288f16243faf58e6bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………………….. than you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "intelligent",
                "more intelligent",
                "most intelligent"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8cefc60511134045b014c2a1e9396703"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is the …………………………. boy in the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "clever",
                "cleverer",
                "cleverest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "993917676079436f8a07be66f355c3c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "These days, I am …………………………… than I used to be.",
            "description": "Use a comparative adjective before than. ",
            "answers": [
                "happy",
                "happier",
                "happiest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c598b4aa0ed24b248778ae748d03733f"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ………………………… than that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bright",
                "brighter",
                "more bright"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "589e1e8aaebd4de4a7ed67594abd89ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is the …………………………… man in my village.",
            "description": "The superlative is used to compare one person or thing to the whole group to which they/it belong(s).",
            "answers": [
                "old",
                "older",
                "oldest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b0a01400d64641ca974b9fcab5fe9817"
        },
        {
            "question": "She earns …………………………… than me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "much",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "069a62b286704eadbf8498c3213186ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "She looks …………………………… than she is.",
            "description": "Use a comparative adjective before than.",
            "answers": [
                "young",
                "younger",
                "youngest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c13dbb580c9b447f87dbdca61f2c96d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is as ………………………….. as that.",
            "description": "Use a positive adjective in the structure as... as....",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "well",
                "better"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f366cf4bb9634703ac4d2a1bce517b58"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are no …………………………… than him.",
            "description": "Use a comparative expression before than.",
            "answers": [
                "wise",
                "wiser",
                "wisest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "94982a4fa3f343559e2808da85f72947"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is no ………………………….",
            "description": "When there is no idea of comparison, use the positive adjective. ",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "better",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7bb1ca0527cc445ea672d8128f8ed064"
        },
        {
            "question": "How is your grandmother today? Is she any ……………………………?",
            "description": "When change is implied, use the comparative form. ",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "better",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3ec1af90ff264a6ea2e8bc23a640b7ea"
        }
    ]
}